<<$1FC8F1:0.part1>>
[20][20]Several years after the         Cyber Clone Incident, a new     dread fell upon the people.                                     Hundreds of cases of            abduction. The emergence        of unidentified life-forms.     And militants calling           themselves "Peacekeepers"       appeared.                                                       Not one soul realized           this string of incidents        was the work of Krummbach's     "Messiah Project."                                              To a government at its          wits' end over how to           handle the unidentified         life-forms, a single            document arrived.               A development proposal          for the "Metal Frame."                                          The sender: Krummbach           Lorinzam. A figure once         renowned, alongside Doctor      Barclay, for the development    of the wonder drug,             "Jecusyn."                                                      The government accepted the     proposal, and turned over a     subsidy, along with the         artificial island left          abandoned since the Cyber       Clone Incident, as his          development factory.                                            Krummbach founded Douglas       Motor Corporation, pressing     Metal Frame development         forward. And, all the while,    his true plan was advancing     as well...                                                      No one, at that point in        time, could have known          what impact the founding        of Douglas Motor Corp.          would have upon humanity.                                                                                                                                                                       And so today, society is        being swallowed by the          ever-growing shadow that is     Douglas Motor Corporation...                                                                                                                                                                [FF]
<<$1FC8F1:0.part2>>
[10][20] "Human history is               the history of war."                                            Such words are                  spoken as though                they were a matter              of course, as                   commonplace truth.                                              Desire gives birth              to progress; peace              itself craves war.                                              That such repetition            is the history of               humankind- if that be           so, it is far too sad.                                                                          And as for people-              for what end are they           born? What is it they           strive to do?...                                                This answer I have              yet to find, but until          it is truly known, I            wish to record this             era of ours just as             it stands, and go               on doing so.                                                                                    "Believing in the               wisest of all that              lives- in mankind..."                                                   Maria Norton                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                               [FF]
