<<$1FC8F1:0.part1>>
[20][20]Several years after the         Cyber Clone Incident, a new     dread fell upon the people.                                     Hundreds of cases of ab-        duction, the emergence of       unidentified life-forms,        then, militants calling         themselves "Peacekeepers,"      appeared.                                                       Not one soul realized           this string of incidents        was the work of Krummbach's     "Messiah Project."                                              To a government stymied by      the sudden emergence of         unidentified life-forms, a      single document arrived.        It was a development            proposal for the "Metal         Frame."                                                         The sender; Krummbach           Lorinzam. A figure once         renowned, alongside Doctor      Barkley, for the development    of the wonder drug,             "Jecusyn."                                                      The government accepted the     proposal, and turned over a     subsidy along with the arti-    ficial island left abandoned    since the Cyber Clone           Incident, as his development    factory.                                                        Krummbach founded Douglas       Motor Corp. and pressed         Metal Frame development         forward. And, in parallel,      his true plan...                                                What impact the founding of     Douglas Motor Corp. would       have upon humanity, none at     that point in time could        have known.                                                                                                                                                                                                                     And so today, society is        being drawn beneath the         looming shadow that is the      Douglas Motor Corporation...                                                                                                                                                                [FF]
<<$1FC8F1:0.part2>>
[10][20] "Human history is               the history of war."                                            Such words are                  oft spoken as if a              matter of course,               as commonplace truth.                                           Desire gives birth to           progress; and peace             itself calls forth war.                                                                         That such repetition            is the history of               humankind- if uttered,          it is far too sad.                                                                              And we ourselves-               for what end are we             born? What is it we             strive to do?...                                                This answer I have              yet to find, but until          it is truly known, I            would record this era           of ours just as it              stands.                                                         Such is my wish.                                                "Believing in the               wisest of all that              lives: in mankind..."                                                   Maria Norton                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                               [FF]
